Guide to the Yale School of Drama Photographs and Posters
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of Yale School of Drama productions, 1966-1992; Accession 2008-A-071
  - Walk the Dog Willie, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 92-93)
  - The Tempest, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 94-96)
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 97-99)
  - Brochure, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 100-101)
  - The Vietnamization of New Jersey, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 102-103)
  - The Durang Flash, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 104-105)
  - The Banquet Years, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 106-107)
  - Mr. Puntilla and His Chaffeur, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 108-109)
  - Dynamite Tonight, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 110-111)
  - Ivanov, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 112-113)
  - Julius Caesar, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 114-116)
  - Suicide in B Flat, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 117-118)
  - White Marriage, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 119-120)
  - B Beaver Animation, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Sganarelle, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 122-123)
  - The Wild Duck, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 124-125)
  - Wings, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 126-127)
  - Terra Nova, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 128-129)
  - The Bundle, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 130-131)
  - Mistaken Identities, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 132-133)
  - Man is Man, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 134-135)
  - Tales from the Vienna Woods, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 136-137)
  - The 1940s Radio Hour, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 138-139)
  - Reunion, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - The Seagull, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 141-142)
  - Jacques Brel, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 143-144)
  - As You Like It, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 145-146)
  - Buried Child, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 147-148)
  - Mahagonny, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 149-150)
  - Ghost Sonata, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 151-153)
  - Timon of Athens, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 154-156)
  - Bosoms and Neglect, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - They Are Dying Out, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Measure for Measure, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 159-161)
  - The Curse of the Starving Class, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 162-163)
  - Lessons from Aioes, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 164-166)
  - Ubu Rex, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 167-168)
  - Boesman and Lena, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 169-170)
  - The Suicide, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Hedda Gabler, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - The Magnificent Cuckoold, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - An Attempt at Flying, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Winterfest 1, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 175-177)
  - Network Day, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Twelth Night, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 179-180)
  - Uncle Vanya, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 181-183)
  - Rip Van Winkle, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Johnny Bull, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Master Harold and the Boys, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 187-188)
  - Love's Labours Lost, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 189-190)
  - Winterfest 2, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 191-193)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 194-196)
  - About Face, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 197-199)
  - A Touch of the Poet, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 200-202)
  - A Doll's House, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 203-205)
  - Hello and Goodbye, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 206-208)
  - The Philanderer, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 209-211)
  - Winterfest 3, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 212-214)
  - Major Barbara, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 215-216)
  - A Raisin in the Sun, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 217-218)
  - Richard II, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 219-221)
  - Night is the Mother to Day, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 222-224)
  - Winterfest 4, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 225-226)
  - Tartuffe, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 227-229)
  - A Play of Giants, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 230-232)
  - Henry IV Pt 1, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 233-235)
  - What the Butler Saw, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 236-238)
  - Talley's Folly, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 239-241)
  - Winterfest 5, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 242-245)
  - Little Eyolf, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 247-248)
  - Othello, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 249-250)
  - Blood Knot, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 251-253)
  - Marriage, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 254-255)
  - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 256-257)
  - Elizabeth, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 258-259)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 260)
  - Neopolitan Ghosts, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 261-262)
  - Heartbreak House, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 263-264)
  - A Place with the Pigs, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 265-266)
  - Winterfest 7, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 267-269)
  - A Walk in the Woods, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 270-271)
  - Melons, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 272-273)
  - Sarcophagus, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 274-275)
  - The Miser, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 276-277)
  - Long Day's Journey into Night, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 278-280)
  - Ah! Wilderness, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 281-282)
  - Winterfest 8, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 283-284)
  - Intermezzo, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 285-286)
  - Kiss of the Spiderwoman, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 287-288)
  - The Alchemist, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 289-290)
  - Moon Over Miami, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - Warrior Ant, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Playboy of the West Indies, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - Cobb, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - Winterfest 9, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - Miss Julie, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 296-297)
  - Summer and Smoke, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 298-299)
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - Pygmalion, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 301-302)
  - The Solid Gold Cadillac, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Winterfest 10, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Ivanov, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 305-306)
  - Largo Desolato, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 307-308)
  - Search and Destroy, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 309-310)
  - Underground, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 311-312)
  - Scapin, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 313-314)
  - A Moon for the Misbegotten, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 315-316)
  - Winterfest 11, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Fefu and Her Friends, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 318-319)
  - The Death of the Last Black Man in America, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Democracy in America, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - Winterfest 12, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 322-323)
  - A Walk in the Woods (NYC?), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Posters
    - Season poster (Box 5)
    - Eurydice (Box 5)
    - In the Continuum (Box 5)
    - Black Snow and Characters (Box 5)
    - Unmentionables (Box 5)
    - Holiday (Box 5)
    - Hamlet (Box 6)
    - Duchess of Malfi (Box 6)
- Photographs, 1923-1980; Accession 2008-A-107
  - Yale School of Drama class of 1923 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yale School of Drama class of 1927 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Yale School of Drama class of 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - John Brown's Body, Macbeth cast, A Touch of the Poet, untitled, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Brief Candle, Chastelard, No More Frontier, Overlords, Spring o' the Year candid and technical, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Contact Sheets, undated
    - A-Dea (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dec-0 (Box 2, Folder 8A)
    - P-X (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Peter Grimes, Heat, Lower Depths, undated (Box 2, Folder 9A)
  - Donated by alumni, 1929-1965
    - 1929-1932 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1934-1936 (Box 2, Folder 10A)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1958-1965 (Box 2, Folder 11A)
  - Donated by patrons, 1915, 1958, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Faculty, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Newman, Paul, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Weaver, Sigourney, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - University Theatre, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Productions, 1925-1980
    - Adam, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Agamemnon, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Aliens from the Commonwealth, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - All People, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - American Primitive, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - American Wing, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Andromache, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - And Such Small Deer, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Another Summer, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Arden of Faversham, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Arms and the Man, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - As Mortal Man, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - At the Seventh Hour, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - At War with the Army, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Bachelor of Arts, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - A Ball for the Imagination, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Barchester Towers, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Beethoven, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Better Days, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Beware of the Bull, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - The Birds Are Wiser, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Bound East for Cardiff, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Le Bourgeois Gentilhomme, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Bow Down, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Brand, 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Bride Ship, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - The Bridge, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - The Bridge and the Bumblebee, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Brief Candle, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Busybodies, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - But Not for Love, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Caesar and Cleopatra, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Casina, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Chanticleer, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Charity Ball, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Chastelard, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - The Cherry Orchard, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Children of the Ladybug, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - The Circle of Chalk, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Cloud Mountain, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Culbin Sands, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Cock-A-Doodle Dandy, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Comedy on the Bridge, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Companions on the Left Hand, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Coriolanus, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Coronation, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - The Crab, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Crabapple, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Decade, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Deep Waters, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Defiance, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Devil's Disciple, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Dido and Aeneas, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Divine Comedy, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - A Doll's House, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Done Got Over, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Duchess of Malfi, undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - The Duel, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Dust to Earth, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - The Emperor Jones, 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Everyman, undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - The Fair Maid of the West, undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - The Fan, undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - The Far Smiling Land, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Fashion, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Faust, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Finished, 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - First Came Fire, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - First in Heart, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - The Flowering Peach, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - The Forest, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Forne, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Garden of Time, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - The Ghose Sonata, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Gideon, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Gift of Gold, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - The Goblin, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - The God Innis, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - The Golden Legend of Pansy Doty, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - The Good Lieutenant, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - The Great Excitement, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - The Greatest Man in the World, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Hamlet, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Hans Bulow's Last Puppet, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Happy As Larry, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - He Who Must Die, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Heartbreak House, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Henry IV, Part 1, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Here Comes Santa Claus, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - High Cockalorum, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Highland Fling, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Homecoming, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Hospital Scene, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - House Afire, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - The House of Jukes, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - House of the Basilisk, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Illusion, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Improper Guardianship, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Indian Wind, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Inspector General, undated (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - The Institute, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - It's Morning, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - I've Met You Before, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Jack Rabbit Flats, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - J.B., 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Jew from Malta, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Job's Brethren, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - John Brown's Body, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - John Doe, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Keepers of the House, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Key to Liberty, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - King of Nowhere, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - The King's Coat, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Knights of the Roundtable, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - "L", 1947 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - The Land of Nobody, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Lazy, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Legend of Lovers, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Listen My Children, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - The Little Immortal, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - The Little Ming Horses, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Loopety-Light, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Lost Sheep, undated (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Lottie Gathers No Moss, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Love and Intrigue, undated (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Love in Buffalo, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Love in Parentheses, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Macbeth, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Machiavelli, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Major Barbara, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Man and the Masses, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Man Better Man, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 148A)
    - A Man of Distinction, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - The Man of Mode, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Mannequin's Maid, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Maria Magdalena, undated (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Martha Goodwin's Possession, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Masquerade, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Measure for Measure, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - The Menaechmi, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Mennonite, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - The Mercenary Match, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - The Merchant, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Merry Go Round, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Merry Wives of Windsor, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Mighty Ghost o' the Lower Gunk, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Minnie Field, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Misalliance, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - The Miser, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Miss Buell, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Murder in the Cathedral, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Mogo and the People, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Mona, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Murder is Fun, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - The Murderers, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - The Myrmidons, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Names in Bronze, 1934 (Box 4A, Folder 174)
    - Naropa, 1978-1979 (Box 4A, Folder 175)
    - Never Sardines, 1932 (Box 4A, Folder 176)
    - No More Frontier, 1930 (Box 4A, Folder 177)
    - On Wings of Song, 1935 (Box 4A, Folder 178)
    - Once Upon a Time, 1939 (Box 4A, Folder 179)
    - One Act Plays, 1940 (Box 4A, Folder 180)
    - One Act Plays, 1942 (Box 4A, Folder 181)
    - One Act Plays, 1945 (Box 4A, Folder 182)
    - One Act Plays, 1946 (Box 4A, Folder 183)
    - One Act Plays, 1946 (Box 4A, Folder 184)
    - One Act Plays, 1947 (Box 4A, Folder 185)
    - One Act Plays, 1949 (Box 4A, Folder 186)
    - One Shall Be, 1935 (Box 4A, Folder 187)
    - Orphee, 1935 (Box 4A, Folder 188)
    - Othello, 1965-1966 (Box 4A, Folder 189)
    - Our Husband Has Gone Mad Again, 1966 (Box 4A, Folder 190)
    - Our Town, 1944 (Box 4A, Folder 191)
    - Overlords, 1928 (Box 4A, Folder 192)
    - Parade, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Paris Leave, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Passee, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - The Passing of the Kwongs, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - The Patriarch, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Peer Gynt, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Peking Politics, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - People on the Hill, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Phaedra, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - The Pink Pigeon, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - The Playboy of the Western World, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Privacy, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - The Prologue, undated (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Prometheus Bound, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Pueblo, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Retreat, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Ribbon Bound, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Right You Are, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - The Rivals, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Rogue in a Bed, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Roots in the Wasteland, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Round Trip, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Saint's Parade, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - The Seagull, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - The Searcher, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - The Seed and the Thorn, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - She Stoops to Compromise, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Shoe the Wild Mare, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - The Simple Life, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Skinflint, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Smith of Stratford, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - The Snows of Kilimanjaro, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Solo Flight, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - The Song of the Broken Horn, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Spring o' the Year, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - The Stars Set, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Steel, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Sunset Crowd, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Taken from Life, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - The Tempest, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Terry by Terry, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - The Fallow Ground, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Things is That-A-Way, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Three Sisters, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Thy Son is Right, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Time of Your Life, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Tin Top Valley, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - A Touch of the Poet, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Third Floor West, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Thy Will Be Done, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - The Trial, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Trout in the Stew, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - True and Special Friend, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Uncle Harry, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Uncommon Women and Others, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - The Unexpected Truth, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Uptown, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Venice Preserved, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - The Visit, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Volpone, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - The Voyage, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - The Wedding, undated (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - The Wedge, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - A Wee Diamond Ring, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Welcome Home, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - What's a Fixer For, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - What to Be, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Wheat in the Fields, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - The Wheel, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - Where There's A Will, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - Winds in the Grass, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - The Winter's Tale, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - Winterset, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - The Worm, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Xanthius and Charmian, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - Yerma, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - Coal Dust, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - There's No Money in Polky, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 271)
- Photographic negatives, slides and clippings documenting performances, 1984-2002; Accession 2009-A-030
  - Unsorted Photo Negatives
    - Dave Nelson Headshots, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Theresa McElide (?) Headshots (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Christmas Card, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Commencement, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - True West (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Fences Headshots (LaJara Henderson, Cristal Coleman) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Phonathon, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Talley's Folly Press Shot (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Summer Cabaret, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Winterfest, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Class Photos, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Architectural/Landscape Photos (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 60th Weekend, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dario Fo -Franca Rame (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Commencement, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Blood Knot NYC Party (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Exxon Luncheon (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - L. Lortel Award (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Cole NYC (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Rep Lobby -Sub. Sales (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Christmas Party (Algonquin Hotel) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University Theatre Seats Removed (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Yale Theatre Circle -NYC (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Christmas Card, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Class Photos, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Heartbreak House Props (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Winter's Tale Headshots (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Winterfest 1st Rehearsal (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Neapolitan Ghosts Headshots, Rehearsal (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Almost by Chance a Woman: Elizabeth 1st Reh. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - A Place With the Pigs 1st Rehearsal (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous YSD Shows, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Divinity, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Forestry & Environmental Science (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Commencement, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Summer Cabaret, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Lloyd Richards Tony Award (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Christmas Card, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Class Photos, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University Theatre Exterior (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Student Subscription Brochure (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Winterfest, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Class Photos, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Class Photos, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous YSD Shows (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Beef, No Chicken Photo Slides (YRT), 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Troilus and Cresside Production Photo (YRT), 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Way of the World Photo Proofs (YRT), 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Skriker Photo Slides (YSD), 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - You Never Can Tell Photo Negatives (YRT), 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Master and Margarita Photo Slides (YSD), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Our Town Photo Slides (YSD), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire Photo Slides (YSD), 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Kingdom of Earth Photo Slides (YRT), 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - It Pays to Advertise Photo Slides (YRT), 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Betty's Summer Vacation Photo Slides (YRT), 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - YSD Press Clippings, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - YRT Press Clippings, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Yale School of Drama posters, 1998-2003; Accession 2009-A-092
  - Peter and Wendy, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Measure for Measure, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Hay Fever, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Glass Menagerie, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Betrayal, 1999 (Box 1)